vaughn.live 2019-11-03

# Privacy - Vaughn Live

Privacy 

_(Updated May 24, 2018)_

**Your Privacy**

VaughnSoft (each, a "VaughnSoft Web Service," "VaughnSoft Web Services," "Vaughn," "VaughnSoft," "[vn]," "[vn] Vaughn," "Vaughn Software," "Vaughn Network," "Vaughn Chat Robot," "Vaughn Gaming," "Vaughn Bot," "Vaughn Live," the Vaughn Live logo and collectively, the "VaughnSoft Services") believes your privacy is very important. Continued use of VaughnSoft Services constitutes your agreement of this policy. 

**Cookies**

VaughnSoft utilizes cookies to store information about your browsing session, browser, and to identify your browser for authentication (Example: cookies stored to remember you are signed in) 

**IP Address**

Your IP Address identifies who you are on the internet. VaughnSoft logs your IP Address for many uses, one for getting an accurate count of users browsing VaughnSoft, another to protect itself if need be, be it by blocking said IP Address or by handing it over to authorities. We also may use third party services to check if your IP Address is a threat to the safety and stability of the VaughnSoft Services 

**Email Address**

We use a third party service to verify deliverability and validity of email addresses submitted to VaughnSoft. This is also done to help prevent abuse of our services and members. We also use a third party service to deliver critical emails (such as notifictions, account creation, forgot password) to your inbox. We do not sell your email and we never will. 

**Messages, Comments, Blogs & other means of electronic communication**

Any message, comments, blogs or other data submitted by you, the user, may be used, viewed, removed or distributed as we see fit. If you do not agree with this, do not send/receive any messages, send/receive any comments, post blogs 

**Photos**

Any photos you upload to VaughnSoft may be used, viewed, removed or distributed as we see fit. If you do not agree with this, simply do not upload any photos. 

**Anayltics and Service Protection**

We have our own in-house anayltics system based on IP Addresses, Cookies, and anonymous Browser information. This data is used to calculate relevant statistics (such as channel views). We also store IP Addresses, Cookies, and anonymous Browser information (where applicable) across all VaughnSoft Services your device connects to. Our VaughnSoft Services also temporarily stores data, such as IP Addresses, Cookies, and anonymous Browser information, to handle user sessions within that VaughnSoft Services server memory. 

**Third Party Analytics**

VaughnSoft Services utilizes Google Analytics as a means to measure traffic stats and other relevant data for statistical purposes. 

**General Information/data**

Any other information/data not covered in this document will be under the notion that VaughnSoft will be used, viewed, removed or distributed as it sees fit. If you do not agree with this, please do not use VaughnSoft Services. 

**Security**

VaughnSoft does what it can to provide the best security for your VaughnSoft account, however, we cannot guarantee your account and information will be 100% safe. We can only do so much, you must also take precautions to keep your account and information safe. VaughnSoft is not responsible for your account and/or information, you are. By using VaughnSoft, you agree to this. 

**EEA Residents**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area ("EEA"), you can make requests regarding your personal data under the GDPR regulation. We will comply with requests to exercise these rights in accordance with applicable law. We will continue to utilize data for legitimate interests (such as protecting our business, for example) and/or in compliance of legal requirement. Please note that we require extensive identification to ensure we are compliance with data safety laws and to ensure requests for your personal data only come from you. Below is a list of personal data you may request: 

\- Get a copy of specific personal data may have about you   
\- Delete or update specific personal data about you   
\- End your agreement with VaughnSoft to process certain personal information about you (this will result in termination and blocking of access to all of our services)   
\- Limit how specific personal data is handled, processed, or disclosed about you.   
\- Prevent use of specific personal data being used for direct marketing purposes   
\- Transfer specific personal data to a third party (which doesn't make much sense, given the types of services VaughnSoft offers 

If you have any further questions, please do not hesitate to contact VaughnSoft's support team [ contact@vaughnsoft.com ]. If your situation requires, you may file a complaint to the data protection supervisory authority in the country you are located. We encourage you to contact us first to resolve any issues or concers you may have. 

**Data Controller Information**

VaughnSoft, located at 411 Malibu Canyon Drive, Columbia, TN 38401, is the "data controller" of your personal data that you submitted to VaughnSoft Services. 

**Children's Privacy**

If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access VaughnSoft at any time or in any manner. Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, VaughnSoft does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 18 years-of-age. If VaughnSoft learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 18 years-of-age has been collected on or through VaughnSoft, then VaughnSoft will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 18 who has/is using VaughnSoft service(s), please contact VaughnSoft at: contact [AT] vaughnsoft [DOT] com (replace [AT] and [DOT] with @ and .) to have that child's account terminated and information deleted. 

**Privacy Policy Terms**

VaughnSoft reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time it chooses and without notification. VaughnSoft will provide a "last modified" date located at the top of this Privacy Policy.
